Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Faculty records, 1965 - 1983; F-23-6; 51 cm of textual records
  - Faculty - D, 1982 - 1983; F-23-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - D, 1978 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - E, 1979 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - G, 1981; F-23-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - G, 1976 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - G, 1976 - 1978; F-23-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - H, 1981; F-23-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - H, 1981 - 1983; F-23-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - H, 1978 - 1979; F-23-6-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - J, 1978 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - K, 1978 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - K, 1978 - 1983; F-23-6-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - K, 1981; F-23-6-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - K, 1980 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - K, 1974 - 1978; F-23-6-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - K, 1981 - 1982; F-23-6-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - K, 1982; F-23-6-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - L, 1979 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - L, 1980; F-23-6-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 23-36)
  - Faculty - M, 1980; F-23-6-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - M, 1980 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - M, 1977 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - M, 1966 - 1978; F-23-6-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - M, 1968 - 1978; F-23-6-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - M, 1980; F-23-6-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - M, 1980 - 1982; F-23-6-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - N, 1981; F-23-6-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - P, 1980 - 1982; F-23-6-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - R, 1980 - 1982; F-23-6-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - R, 1980; F-23-6-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - R, 1980; F-23-6-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - R, 1976 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - R, 1976 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 23-37)
  - Faculty - R, 1979; F-23-6-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - R, 1976 - 1979; F-23-6-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - S, 1976; F-23-6-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - S, 1974 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - S, 1981 - 1982; F-23-6-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - S, 1965 - 1974; F-23-6-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - S, 1982; F-23-6-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - S, 1980; F-23-6-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - T, 1975 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - T, 1973 - 1977; F-23-6-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - T, 1980 - 1982; F-23-6-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - T, 1978; F-23-6-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - V, 1971 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - W, 1978 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - W, 1978 - 1979; F-23-6-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 23-38)
  - Faculty - Z, 1979 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 23-38)